const moviesQuestions = [
    {
        id: 0,
        question: "Who is the main protagonist of 'The Wedding Party' and what is their occupation?",
        answer: "Dunni, Fashion Designer"
    },
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "Which character serves as the comedic relief in 'The Wedding Party' and provides humorous moments?",
        answer: "Sola, the best man"
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "Name one of the supporting characters who is a family member of the bride or groom.",
        answer: "Dozie's mother, Tinuade Coker"
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "Which character plays the role of the wedding planner in 'The Wedding Party'?",
        answer: "Wonu, played by Sola Sobowale"
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "Who is the antagonist or source of conflict in 'The Wedding Party'?",
        answer: "The source of conflict in 'The Wedding Party' is mainly the clash between the families of the bride and groom"
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "Who is the central character around whom the story of 'Chief Daddy' revolves?",
        answer: "Chief Daddy himself, played by Nkem Owoh"
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "Who portrayed the character of Neo in 'The Matrix' film trilogy?",
        answer: "Keanu Reeves"
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "Which character acts as the voice of reason or tries to maintain harmony within the family in Chief Daddy?",
        answer: "Jide, played by Falz"
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "Who are the primary antagonists or sources of conflict in 'Chief Daddy'?",
        answer: "The primary antagonists in 'Chief Daddy' are the family members who are vying for Chief Daddy's wealth and property."
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "Who is the main protagonist of 'King of Boys' and what is her role in society?",
        answer: "Eniola Salami, and she is a powerful businesswoman and underworld figure"
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "Which actor won an Academy Award for his role in the film 'The Revenant'?",
        answer: "Leonardo DiCaprio"
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        question: "Which character serves as a trusted ally or right-hand person to the protagonist?",
        answer: "Makanaki, played by Reminisce,  serves as a trusted ally and right-hand person to Eniola Salami"
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        question: "Who is the primary antagonist or opposing force that the protagonist must confront IN KING OF BOYS?",
        answer: "Alhaji Ademola, a corrupt politician who poses a threat to Eniola Salami's power"
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        question: "Name one of the supporting characters who provided comic relief in 'King of Boys'.",
        answer: "Odogwu Malay, played by Illbliss."
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        question: "Which actor played the character of Tony Stark/Iron Man in the Marvel Cinematic Universe?",
        answer: "Robert Downey Jr."
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        question: "Who portrayed the character of Harry Potter in the film series based on J.K. Rowling's novels?",
        answer: "Daniel Radcliffe"
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        question: "Which actor is known for his role as Jack Sparrow in the 'Pirates of the Caribbean' film series?",
        answer: "Johnny Depp"
    },
    {
        id: 15,
        question: "Who starred as Batman in Christopher Nolan's 'The Dark Knight' trilogy?",
        answer: "Christian Bale"
    },
    {
        id: 16,
        question: "5.Which actress played the lead role of Katniss Everdeen in 'The Hunger Games' film series?",
        answer: "Katniss Everdeen "
    },
    {
        id: 17,
        question: "Who starred as the iconic character James Bond in the film 'Casino Royale'?",
        answer: "Daniel Craig"
    },
    {
        id: 18,
        question: "Which actress received critical acclaim for her performance in the film 'Black Swan' and won an Academy Award for it?",
        answer: "Natalie Portman"
    },
    {
        id: 19,
        question: "Who played the character of Hannibal Lecter in the film 'The Silence of the Lambs' and won an Academy Award for the role?",
        answer: "Anthony Hopkins"
    },
]

export { moviesQuestions }